[
    {
           "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
           "optionA": "Dog",
           "optionB": "Elephant",
           "optionC": "Goat",
           "optionD": "Lion",
           "answer": "Elephant"
       },
       {
        "question": "When was IPL started",
        "optionA": "2008",
        "optionB": "2009",
        "optionC": "2007",
        "optionD": "2006",
        "answer": "2007"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player has made highest numbers of runs in IPL history?",
        "optionA": "Suresh Raina",
        "optionB": "Virat Kohli",
        "optionC": "Chris Gayle",
        "optionD": "Murli Vijay",
        "answer": "Virat Kohli"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player has taken most numbers of wickets in IPL so far?",
        "optionA": "Lasith Malinga",
        "optionB": "Ravindra Jadeja",
        "optionC": " Zaheer Khan",
        "optionD": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Lasith Malinga"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team has never won the IPL tournament?",
        "optionA": "Deccan Chargers",
        "optionB": "Sunrisers Hyderabad",
        "optionC": " Rajasthan Royals",
        "optionD": "Royal Challengers Bangalore",
        "answer": "Royal Challengers Bangalore"
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximum how many foreign players can play in the playing eleven of the IPL match??",
        "optionA": "3",
        "optionB": "5",
        "optionC": "4",
        "optionD": "Not fixed, depends on the decision of captain of the team",
        "answer": "Not fixed, depends on the decision of captain of the team"
    },{
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
     "question": "When was IPL started",
     "optionA": "2008",
     "optionB": "2009",
     "optionC": "2007",
     "optionD": "2006",
     "answer": "2007"
 },
 {
     "question": "Which player has made highest numbers of runs in IPL history?",
     "optionA": "Suresh Raina",
     "optionB": "Virat Kohli",
     "optionC": "Chris Gayle",
     "optionD": "Murli Vijay",
     "answer": "Virat Kohli"
 },
 {
     "question": "Which player has taken most numbers of wickets in IPL so far?",
     "optionA": "Lasith Malinga",
     "optionB": "Ravindra Jadeja",
     "optionC": " Zaheer Khan",
     "optionD": "None of the above",
     "answer": "Lasith Malinga"
 }
       
       
   ]